The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Red Butterfly !
You indeed know me.
Speak,
who the hell are you ?
Who doesn't know Xue Yue's genius ?
Not going to tell me ?
Then you will
remain here forever !
This is her domain !
Master, what's going on ?
Wake up !
Early stage Soul Formation...
If you don't struggle,
you can have a painless death.
My memories and emotions
are becoming numb...
Wan'er...
I hate you !!!
I never believed in fate !
She's already gone.
I told you not to tell her.
It's all your fault !
You... You...
Enough !
If I were to get lost in this emotionless domain,
I'll never be the same again.
I would become an emotionless murderer.
Life and death are controlled by her thoughts.
Her domain
is capable of freezing emotions.
The domain of this genius
is so domineering.
If I can't break her domain,
I'll be in deep trouble.
This snow is born in the sky
and dies on the earth.
I heard Red Butterfly managed to reach Peak Late stage Soul Formation
in a mere 100 years.
100 years is the lifetime of a mortal.
I wonder if your parents
are still alive.
Red Butterfly,
do your parents have
any other children ?
If not, doesn’t that mean they have no one to send them off ?
That means you are... unfilial.
Know your place !
Your domain
is too weak.
Instead of collapsing,
his domain is spreading out.
As long as I can kill him...
For 100 years,
mortals have lived.
Was your family
wiped out by the law of the heavens ?
Red Butterfly,
even if your parents are dead,
they will always be looking at you.
Do you dare to look back at them !?
The Icy Snow Tactic
requires a clear heart.
That's why I was suspicious.
Red Butterfly has only cultivated for 100 years.
No matter her talent,
she couldn't have wiped all her emotions.
Love never dies.
Naturally, her Dao Heart is unstable.
Dragon Restriction, attack !
A mere Early stage Soul Formation
tried to ruin my Dao Heart.
I can't allow him to live !
Master,
that woman has a higher cultivation than you.
Why are you so chill about it ?
She...
She is going to catch up with us !
You can't escape.
Master, what are you doing ?!
Run away !
I won't run away.
This is...
You !
He has access to teleportation formations
so his identity must not be exceptional.
His Dao Heart is strong,
he's very cautious,
has a strange domain,
and extraordinary artifacts.
He must be the most elite disciple
of a rank 5 country of Suzaku.
Rain Celestial Realm\NLava fragment
That palm strike was empty
but it managed to fool Red Butterfly.
Otherwise, with our gap in cultivation,
it would have been hard to escape.
I almost ran out of spiritual energy...
This palm strike was really expensive.
Spatial rifts ?
There are spatial rifts ahead
and lava below,
even if there is a treasure here, it must be ruined.
Why did the Da Lou Sword Sect build the teleportation formation here ?
There must be something inside this cave.
This place is very strange.
But it's too dangerous to enter alone.
I need to wait for other people,
that's my best chance.
3 days later
So they have come.
Third Senior Brother,
is this the Celestial Beast Temple ?
Correct.
Zheng Hao\NDa Lou Sword Sect disciple\NEarly stage Soul Formation
This place
is one of the 16 Celestial Beast Temples.
The Ancestor found this place by accident.
After thousands of years,
this place has been badly damaged.
Sixth Junior Brother, you just reached Soul Formation
You must pay attention to the spacial rifts.
Remember to always have the Full Search Tactic activated.
Da Lou Sword Sect\NFull Search Tactic
This Full Search Tactic
must be able to help them avoid the spacial rifts.
It's very useful in the Celestial Realm.
Celestial Beast Temple\NLava fragment\NRain Celestial Realm
Remember you can't use teleportation inside.
You must be careful.
Third Senior Brother,
this Celestial Beast Temple has been here for so many years
so it should already have been emptied.
Even if there are Celestial Beast Souls remaining,
I'm afraid they would be hard to obtain for just the two of us.
The Celestial Realm lacks spiritual energy.
If there are any
Celestial Beast Souls left,
they must be very weak.
If we bring back one,
we will be rewarded.
Back then, the Ancestor was able to find
a Celestial Beast Soul here.
He then proceeded to unite planet Da Lou.
There's such a treasure ?
No wonder they placed the formation here.
Celestial Beast Temple
Here's some celestial spiritual energy.
Back then, the Ancestor
found a Celestial Beast Soul here.
Junior,
protect me
while I gather this celestial spiritual energy.
Okay.
Da Lou Sword Sect\NSoul Purification Gourd
This gourd can gather celestial spiritual energy much quicker.
Celestial jades
Sixth Junior Brother,
we've got a good harvest this time.
The celestial spiritual energy
was enough for 2 celestial jades.
Keep this one.
This way,
we've both completed the lowest requirement of our sect.
Thank you.
Third Senior Brother,
Is this the Soul Purification Gourd ?
Correct.
This is one of the 3 Soul Purification Gourds
personally refined by the Ancestor.
With this,
we can quickly gather celestial spiritual energy
without wasting time refining it.
What was that sound ?
Celestial Beast Temple\NLava fragment\NRain Celestial Realm
Junior,
go ahead
to see what that ball of light is.
I...
Why does this look familiar ?
Don't be afraid Junior,
your Senior is protecting you.
Go for it.
Get closer !
3 more steps !
Bring the skull here !
Chase !
Senior Brother,
what the hell was that ?
If I'm not mistaken,
this is a Celestial Beast Feed.
It turns out that was a Celestial Beast Feed.
No wonder the mosquito beast loved it.
But compared to those of the Sea of Devils,
this Celestial Beast Feed
is way more powerful.
Mere feed for celestial beasts and it has this much power ?
If that thing had entered my brow,
I would have turned into a skeleton…
You cannot be scared of mere Celestial Beast Feed.
How are you going to be respected in the Da Lou Sword Sect ?
If we can catch that Celestial Beast Feed,
we will rise through the ranks.
Using his Junior's life as a test.
This Senior Brother
is ill-intentioned.
A celestial artifact ?
I found a celestial artifact !
Retreat !
Die !
Two Swords Spirit World !
Senior Brother,
why are there so many Celestial Beast Feeds ?
The aura of that artifact must be too strong.
Under its influence,
the Celestial Beast Feeds grew to such an extent.
It's a disaster !
With our cultivation,
it will be difficult to escape so many Celestial Beast Feeds.
I can only use my Junior's life
to keep me alive.
Junior !
Watch out behind you !
Senior Brother,
what are you doing ?
Sun Lei\NDa Lou Sword Sect disciple\NMiddle stage Soul Formation
Middle stage Soul Formation ?!
You...
Who the hell are you ?
Obtaining a celestial artifact is an unprecedented opportunity.
While the Celestial Beast Feeds are running rampant,
now is my best chance to get it.
Falling from the night sky and melting into dust\Nlike water without a source.
Like the difference between clouds and mud,\Nthe truth cannot be found in conflict.
Life and death\Nare like the moment when the rain falls
and like many other unseparable things.
In this lifetime,\Nto cultivate the truth, cultivate the world first.
Old grudges had to be settled\Nbecause half an inch is engraved into my tree rings.
Use the most vivid love and hate\Nto ask questions to your fate.
Let your eyes be filled enough with rage\Nto pierce the heart and the soul
then soften because of the mortals' fireworks.
Only when you bend down can you understand\Nthe hidden edge of the blade.
The human mind is nature,\Nthe rain fell silently like an answer.
Life and death are just moments away,\Nthere are many other solutions to grudges.
Use your dusty heart\Nto depict the world.
One stroke is for killing.\NAfter struggling for hundreds of years, I endured letting go.
One stroke is for caring.\NEverywhere there is life, there are thousands of lights.
Give up your mind to be refined\Nby this endless world.
The human mind is nature,\Nthe rain fell silently like an answer.
Life and death are just moments away,\Nthere are many other solutions to grudges.
Use your dusty heart\Nto depict the world.
One stroke is for killing.\NAfter struggling for hundreds of years, I endured letting go.
One stroke is for caring.\NEverywhere there is life, there are thousands of lights.
Give up your mind to be refined\Nby this endless world.
Snow falls as my hair turns white, winter withers\Nwhile prosperity sprouts in summer.
I step into the world, with light at my fingertips,\Nthe law of cause and effect.
I observe the vastness of heaven and earth so I can get rid of evil.
Obsession arises from one thought, life and death arise from one thought.\NReincarnation is not to be feared.